<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Wolf</string>
    <string name="poke_club">POKÉ CLUB</string>
    <string name="poke_club_description">Poké Club - originally a dark kitchen - is one of the first in Brussels to offer Poké Bowls. Poke is the main dish of Hawaiian cuisine. Protein, vitamins, fibre… all in one bowl. From a nutritional perspective, it\'s hard to do better. And why not give them an Asian flavour? By mixing rice with marinated fish, vegetables and fruit, for example.</string>
    <string name="dims">DiM’S</string>
    <string name="dims_description">The menu features various dim\'s, bao\'s and noodles : ketjap beef, teriyaki chicken, peking duck, pulled pork, etc. Tradition mixed with innovation, the result is stunning, everything is homemade. That\'s why we are convinced from the first bite, and the steaming baskets pile up on our table.</string>
    <string name="eaters">EATERS</string>
    <string name="eaters_description">Foodies know that nothing beats fresh, high-quality ingredients for a successful street food dish. But where to start? By, like Eaters, successfully baking fresh Bahn-mi rolls, based on a foolproof Vietnamese technique, and then garnishing them with crispy chicken, or pulled beed, or tempura shrimps, with their own homemade sauce. And after that? If you have a little space left, don\'t miss the Bowls, with surprising flavours from the other side of the world. Bites of happiness!</string>
    <string name="poke_club_handle">pokeclubxl</string>
    <string name="dims_handle">dims_experience</string>
    <string name="eaters_handle">eaterskitchens</string>
    <string name="ten_grams">10 GRAMS</string>
    <string name="ten_grams_description">Created by renowned restaurant La Truffe Noire, 10 Grams was inspired by Italian gastronomy and gave it a 3-star twist: every recipe contains black truffles, their speciality. Chef Giorgio explains to us that there are several types of truffles, such as summer black and winter black. The summer black truffle is milder in flavour than the winter truffle and can be used in almost anything, from pasta to ice cream. Stronger in flavour, the winter black truffle has a hint of wood and goes very well with eggs, risottos and pastas, to (re)discover at WOLF.</string>
    <string name="ten_grams_handle">10grams_brussels</string>
    <string name="la_piola_pizza">La Piola Pizza</string>
    <string name="la_piola_pizza_description">La Piola has been voted one of the best pizzerias in Europe several times! From the first bite, you will want to talk to your hands and shout \"Mama mia, quanto sia buono!\" Francesco comes from Naples where he learned all the secrets of the perfect pizza dough. The difference between Neapolitan and other pizzas lies in the art of preparing the dough, which needs to ripe between 24 and 48 hours, and in the way it is baked. Baking is done in an oven at a minimum of 450°C and for a very short time, one to two minutes is enough. When it comes out of the oven, the dough may be slightly less crispy than others, but it is softer and much more digestible.</string>
    <string name="la_piola_pizza_handle">lapiolapizzaofficial</string>
    <string name="mare">Mare</string>
    <string name="mare_description">Imagine North Sea shrimp croquettes as a starter, a sea bass burger as a main course and scrumptious scampi to finish. At Mare, the dishes are fresh and homemade, from croquettes to fish &amp; chips, with a special focus on the sauces that make all the difference. Yummie!</string>
    <string name="dierendonck">Dierendonck</string>
    <string name="dierendonck_description">Hendrik Dierendonck grew up in a family butcher\'s shop. There he learned the trade, choosing and treating the best local meat. Meanwhile, he owns several butchers, has his own restaurant Carcasse, supplies several starred establishments, … and has his own place in Wolf.</string>
    <string name="dierendonck_handle">dierendonck</string>
    <string name="bollyfood_stories">Bollyfood Stories</string>
    <string name="bollyfood_stories_description">Ashok John Alexander is from Delhi, Camille is from Hainaut. He is the chef of three Indian restaurants, and she started out as a waitress in one of them. Together, they are developing a menu of spicy flavours: Chicken Masala, Vegetarian Thali and their new speciality, Naanwiches, are all on the menu. Their aim is to prove that Indian cuisine is delicious, subtile and healthy. An explosion of flavours guaranteed.</string>
    <string name="bollyfood_stories_handle">bollyfoodstories</string>
    <string name="toukoul">Toukoul</string>
    <string name="toukoul_description">In toukouls, the traditional huts in Ethiopia, the cook puts a large wooden bowl in the middle of the table with a mixture of preparations: vegetables, meat, fish, sauces, … Everyone takes a piece of injera, this flat pancake is to Ethiopians what bread is to Belgians, and grabs everyone\'s attention. You experience an explosion of flavours. Toukool\'s cuisine is an experience to try : \"without fork, without knife\". To the table and Bemigibu tedeseti, as we say in Amharic.</string>
    <string name="toukoul_handle">toukoul_restaurant</string>
    <string name="super_filles">Les Super Filles du Tram</string>
    <string name="super_filles_description">Imagine a melt-in-your-mouth Charolais burger, fried onions, cheese, homemade barbecue sauce, finished with a delicious bun. And on top, served with hand-cut fries. You\'re about to bite into a Super Burger: tabarnak, how delicious! The fresh and local vegetables are almost all from organic gardeners; the meat comes from carefully fed cows; there are no frozen foods and that changes everything.</string>
    <string name="super_filles_handle">superfillesdutram</string>
    <string name="mix">Mix</string>
    <string name="mix_description">When you arrive, you\'ll immediately be drawn in by the bright colours, the fruit hanging on the walls and the intoxicating aromas emanating from the kiosk. MIX offers a variety of mouth-watering juices. From classics like freshly squeezed orange juice and apple juice, to special creations like \'Exotic\' (a refreshing blend of mango, pineapple, apple and orange) or \'Green Power\' (a revitalising blend of green apple, spinach, mint and cucumber), there\'s something for everyone.</string>
    <string name="idea">Idea</string>
    <string name="idea_description">Costas and his chefs have developed a unique selection of open pittas, in which we find surprising flavours. For instance, there is a pitta with spetsofai, a classic stewed dish from Greek cuisine. Or, for example, the Greekamole, which Costas developed in Costa Rica. Idea constantly renews itself and dares to make associations that are impossible a priori. And it works! Those who have tasted the mastelo skepasti sandwich, with grilled cheese and cinnamon pears, know why they come, come and come again.</string>
    <string name="idea_handle">ideagreekrestaurants</string>
    <string name="hanoi_station">Hanoi Station</string>
    <string name="hanoi_station_description">Vietnamese cuisine is rich, nutritious, fragrant, sprinkled with spices and fresh herbs. All dosed with tremendous precision to achieve the right balance of each flavour. Pho, a national dish from northern Vietnam, is the ideal breakfast for Vietnamese, even though it is eaten throughout the day. Hanoi Station has made it one of its specialities.</string>
    <string name="hanoi_station_handle">hanoi.station</string>
    <string name="my_tannour">My Tannour</string>
    <string name="my_tannour_description">Addiction warning: a tannour oven is a clay oven in which, among other things, small round buns are baked on a wood fire at a very high temperature. Tradition combined with simplicity and top quality, resulting in delicious street food. My Tannour\'s generous, tasty, fragrant cuisine is a clever blend of different culinary traditions from Syria, Lebanon, Jordan and Iraq. Close your eyes, open your mouth and forget the rest.</string>
    <string name="my_tannour_handle">mytannour.belgium</string>
    <string name="socal_tacos">Socal Tacos</string>
    <string name="socal_tacos_description">From Southern California (SoCal) raised in a Mexican household Maggie and Peter bring you Tacos with corn tortillas and homemade quesadillas. Choose your favorite meat or veggie, add toppings and taste the ultimate Mexican experience ¡Buen Provecho!</string>
    <string name="socal_tacos_handle">socaltacos.belgium</string>
    <string name="mordimi">Mordimi</string>
    <string name="mordimi_description">Mordimi - from the makers of La Piola Pizza - was born out of a desire to bring the famous Neapolitan \"panuozzo\" to Belgium. Mordimi - \"bite me\" in Italian - invites you to re-taste the delicious varieties of Italian charcuterie in purely Mediterranean flavour combinations.</string>
    <string name="mordimi_handle">lapiolapizzaofficial</string>
    <string name="vincent_denis">Vincent Denis</string>
    <string name="vincent_denis_description">Vincent Denis\' signature dessert are highly addictive chocolate marbles. A ball with a flowing centre of milk chocolate and caramel, set on a crispy crumble. There are five different types of marbles, short-lived collections and frozen versions. Vincent Denis is demanding in the choice of raw materials and innovates with different products - such as lemon myrtle leaves from an Australian tree that taste like lemon when crushed. He masters spices perfectly and creates very high-quality dishes with the minute. For those who like simplicity, he also makes the waffles and pancakes of our childhood fun to relive.</string>
    <string name="vincent_denis_handle">vddbofficial</string>
    <string name="bar">Bar</string>
    <string name="bar_description">Rendez-vous at the heart of our food market fiesta, where culinary rebels and flavour thrill-seekers unite and quench their thirst. Try out our craft beers, brewed on the spot in our microbrewery, or one of our excellent home-made lemonades. Our mixologists do magic with cocktails! The classics, or one of our unique signature Wolf cocktails. Or, go wild, and have one of our mocktails. Raise your glass &amp; cheers!</string>
    <string name="bar_handle">wolf.bxl</string>
    <string name="show_more">Toon meer</string>
    <string name="show_less">Toon minder</string>
</resources>